# data of questions and answers
quizlist = [
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is Ross NOT allergic to?",
        "correct_answer": ["Bananas"],
        "incorrect_answers": ["Lobster", "Kiwi","Peanuts"],
        "hint":"In Season 2 Episode 6, The One With the Baby on the Bus, Monica says, 'You’re allergic to lobster, peanuts, and… Oh my god.'The ‘Oh my god’ being kiwi as Ross had just eaten a kiwi-lime pie that Monica had baked, believing it to be a key-lime pie."
    },
    {
        "question": "What's in Monica's locked closet?",
        "correct_answer": ["A whole bunch of junk"],
        "incorrect_answers": ["Candy and chocolate", "Skeletons","Cleaning equipment"],
        "hint": "In Season 8, Chandler finally gets Monica to reveal the contents of that mysterious closet, which is filled with a very un-Monica-like mess"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ross' bald girlfriend was named:",
        "correct_answer": ["Bonnie"],
        "incorrect_answers": ["Beth", "Veronica","Vanessa"],
        "hint": "Ross brings his girlfriend Bonnie on a beach trip in Season 3, only to have Rachel shave her head."
    },
    {
        "question": "What famous person does Phoebe think is her grandfather?",
        "correct_answer": ["Albert Einstein"],
        "incorrect_answers": ["Gary Grant", "Dwight D. Eisenhower","Robert Redford"],
        "hint": "In Season 2's 'The One with Phoebe\'s Dad',Phoebe asks a framed photo of Albert Einstein, whom she thinks is her grandfather, to wish her luck."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Friend has a tattoo?",
        "correct_answer": ["Rachel"],
        "incorrect_answers": ["Monica", "Phoebe","Ross"],
        "hint": "In Season 2's 'The One Where Joey Moved Out', Phoebe and Rachel decide to get tattoos, but Phoebe chickens out and Rachel ends up with a heart tattoo on her hip."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who said, 'Could I BE wearing any more clothes?'",
        "correct_answer": ["Joey"],
        "incorrect_answers": ["Monica", "Gunther","Chandler"],
        "hint": "In Season 3, Joey puts on all of Chandler's clothes (except for underwear) and does lunges."
    },
    {
        "question": "What song does Ross sing to Emma to get her to stop crying?'",
        "correct_answer": ["Baby Got Back"],
        "incorrect_answers": ["Thong Song", "Walk This Way","Sweet Child O'Mine"],
        "hint": "Ross accidentally discovers that singing the suggestive lyrics to 'Baby Got Back' is the only way to get baby Emma to sleep, but he fears telling Rachel about the trick."
    },
    {
        "question": "What toy is always on Joey and Chandler's door?",
        "correct_answer": ["A Magna Doodle"],
        "incorrect_answers": ["A Slinky", "An Etch-a-Sketch","A Wooly Willy"],
        "hint": "The Magna Doodle had a different saying or picture each episode."
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose pizza do the girls get by accident in Season 1?",
        "correct_answer": ["George Stephanopoulous"],
        "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Cruise's", "John F. Kennedy Jr.'s","Ethan Hawke's"],
        "hint": "In 'The One with George Stephanopoulous,' the girls get his pizza and then spy on him from Monica's balcony."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Friend has only nine toes?",
        "correct_answer": ["Chandler"],
        "incorrect_answers": ["Ross", "phoebe","Joey"],
        "hint": "Season 5's 'The One with All the Thanksgivings,' Monica dropped a knife through Chandler's wicker shoes, severing his pinkie toe. She brought a carrot to the hospital instead of his toe. "
    },
]
